tourismthailand.org 2017-06-30

# The official website of Tourism Authority of Thailand

Privacy Policy

You are in control of the information you provide to TourismThailand.org 

As a visitor of TourismThailand.org, you are in complete control of your travel planning needs. This includes controlling the use of information you provide to TourismThailand.org. The bottom line is that we respect and will continue to respect the privacy of our visitors who use TourismThailand.org. 

**1\. WHO DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLY TO?** __

This Privacy Policy applies to the use of TourismThailand.org, participating businesses that voluntarily choose to disclose information for use on the website for tourism purposes, and potential visitors to Thailand who voluntarily choose to become members of TourismThailand.org. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the websites and independent information of companies that are not owned or controlled by TourismThailand.org nor to the people that are not employed or managed by TourismThailand.org, including third party websites that you may be able to connect to through this website. For more information about the sharing of information with third party websites, please see below. 

**2\. WHAT INFORMATION DOES TOURISMTHAILAND.ORG COLLECT?** __

**A. Information that you provide to TourismThailand.org**

In order for us to create your online profile or if you wish to receive Deal Alerts or newsletter subscriptions it will be necessary for you to provide us with some personal information, which are indicated in registration forms with a ‘*’. ****

**User Preferences**

Members can choose to provide TourismThailand.org with travel preferences and other personal information. This information is primarily used to assist members where TourismThailand.org will provide the best information, products, and services to members from time to time. 

**B. Information that TourismThailand.org collects automatically            **

**IP Addresses**

TourismThailand.org collects IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and for system administration. 

Please be aware that we may have third party links on our site which may collect personally identifiable information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices or policies of such Web sites. 

In addition to your IP address, TourismThailand.org collects certain information automatically whenever you visit the website. Some of this information is stored in cookies (see below) or sessions. Examples of other information we collect automatically may include the type of browser and operating system you are using, the times and dates you visit the website, and the Internet address of the website that may have linked you to TourismThailand.org. 

**C. Cookies**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. TourismThailand.org uses cookies in several ways. We use cookies to allow you to login without having to type your login name each time. Instead, only your password is needed to access the system. We also use cookies to track usage of the "Guest" path. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. 

**3\. HOW DOES TOURISMTHAILAND.ORG USE PERSONAL INFORMATION? i.e. Who will the information be shared with?** __

We do not sell individual customer names or other private profile information to third parties and have no intention of doing so in the future. Occasionally, TourismThailand.org will hire a third party to act on our behalf for projects such as marketing campaigns and market research surveys and will provide information to these third parties specifically for use in connection with these projects. The information we provide to such third parties is protected by a confidentiality agreement and is to be used solely for completing the specific projects related to TourismThailand.org, Tourism Authority of Thailand, and its related websites. 

We do not allow third parties to feature advertisements on [TourismThailand.org](http://www.tourismthailand.org/) and there are therefore no third party cookies gathered for advertising purposes. The only third parties that are allowed to post ‘advertisements’ on [TourismThailand.org](http://www.tourismthailand.org/) are non-profit organizations related to governmental agencies. 

**4\. WHAT KIND OF SECURITY DOES TOURISMTHAILAND.ORG USE TO PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY?** __

We know that when you provide us with any type of information, you trust us to keep it safe from unauthorized intrusion. We take all reasonable steps, through the use of updated security software and protocols, to ensure that your personal information is safe.

**5\. HOW CAN YOU CORRECT THE PERSONAL INFORMATION ON RECORD AT TOURISMTHAILAND.ORG?** __

We assume that our users intend the information we collect about them to be complete and accurate and it is important to us that you are able to alter or update any information you find to be inaccurate or incomplete.  We have therefore tried to make it as easy as possible for you to amend any information you provide us in order to ensure that it is truthful and complete. In order to alter your information, please login and click on Your Account Information. If you have any difficulty changing your personal information, please contact a website administrator by filling up the ‘Contact Us’ form. 

**6\. HOW CAN YOU PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?** __

If you wish to protect your personal information, the easiest way is simply to provide as little personal information as possible.  While you must provide certain mandatory requirements about your personal information in order to register with TourismThailand.org, in order to make the optimal use of our website it is beneficial to provide comprehensive and truthful information about yourself. 

However, you may also configure your Web browser to alert you whenever you are about to receive a new cookie, to disable the installation of new cookies, or to disable cookies altogether, but such actions may prevent you from using all the features available on TourismThailand.org.

**Opt Out Policy**

At anytime, you can unsubscribe to any features provided by TourismThailand.org or request that TourismThailand.org does not collect any personal information that is not essential to your inquiry. 

As a member, you will occasionally receive email updates from us about new products, special offers, news, events & festivals, and new TourismThailand.org services. We hope you will find these updates interesting. Of course, if you would rather not receive them, please click on the unsubscribe link in the e-mail message. TourismThailand.org reserves the right to limit membership to those who will accept emails as it is the most effective method for us to reach you. 

**7\. WHAT CAN YOU DO ABOUT VIOLATIONS OF THE TOURISMTHAILAND.ORG’S POLICY?** __

If for any reason you believe the Privacy Policy of TourismThailand.org is incomplete or inaccurate in relation to your user experience, please contact a website administrator here so that we can remedy the situation if necessary. 

**8\. WHAT OTHER INFORMATION SHOULD YOU KNOW ABOUT THE TOURISMTHAILAND.ORG’S PRIVACY POLICY?** __

TourismThailand.org may contain links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you may enter another Web site for which TourismThailand.org has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy Policy of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from TourismThailand.org 's Privacy Policy. Of course, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Please be very careful, responsible, and alert with this information, especially whenever you're online. 

In addition to the circumstances described above, TourismThailand.org may disclose member information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights or properties of TourismThailand.org or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. 

Any material changes in the way TourismThailand.org uses personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Policy. Of course, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our privacy practices to contact email address of TourismThailand.org. Please reference the privacy policy in your subject line. TourismThailand.org will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries. 

**9.** **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY** __

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, when appropriate, you will be notified by e-mail.

**10\. CONTACT** __

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to us by filling up the ‘Contact Us’ form.
